# Inkyu Shin | Curriculum Vitae

☑ dlsrbgg33@kaist.ac.kr

I am a first-year Ph.D. student at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) under the co-supervision of Prof. Kuk-Jin Yoon and Prof. In So Kweon. I earned my B.S and M.S degrees in automotive engineering from Hanyang University(HYU) and KAIST in 2019 and 2021. I was a research intern at NEC Laboratories America, Inc, San Jose, CA.

# **Research Interests**

My research interests currently lie in computer vision. Specifically, I pursue the goal of effectively processing data to build strong and generalizable model in computer vision. Followings are my main research topics.

- Image Translation
- Domain Adaptation and Generalization
- Simulated Learning
- Self-supervised Learning

Ultimately, the purpose of these researches is to apply to a variety of applications (e.g., Autonomous driving, Robot Navigation, AR/VR).

# **Research Experience**

NFC	Laboratories	America.	Inc
115		AIIICIICA.	1110

Research Intern, Supervisor: Yi-Hsuan Tsai.

Korea University

Research Intern, Supervisor: Jaegul Choo.

Hanyang University

Research Assistant, Supervisor: Myuong-Ho Sunwoo

Samsung Electronics

Intern, Semi-conductor Test Group.

San Jose, CA

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Seoul, Korea

Sep 2018 - Dec 2018

Seoul, Korea

Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

Hwasung, Korea

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

#### Education

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

' AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING Ph.D. degree, Advisor: In So Kweon

Daejeon, Korea

2021-

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea

2019–2021

AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING M.S degree, Advisor: In So Kweon
Master's Thesis: Learning to Scale the Labels for Self-training based Domain Adaptation

Hanyang University (HYU)

AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING B.S degree

Seoul, Korea

2013-2019

#### **Publications**

(C: conference / J: journal / P: preprint / \* :equal contributions)

# International Conference.

- [P1] Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Video Semantic Segmentation Kwanyong Park\*, Inkyu Shin\*, Sanghyun Woo, In So Kweon arXiv, 2021
- [C5] LabOR: Labeling Only if Required for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Inkyu Shin, Dong-Jin Kim, Jae Won Cho, Sanghyun Woo, Kwanyong Park, In So Kweon International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2021 (Oral)
- [C4] Discover, Hallucinate, and Adapt:
   Open Compound Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation
   Kwanyong Park, Sanghyun Woo, Inkyu Shin, In So Kweon
   Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2020
- [C3] Two-phase Pseudo Label Densification for Self-training based Domain Adaptation Inkyu Shin, Sanghyun Woo, Fei pan, In So Kweon European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020
   Also presented at "Visual Learning with Limited Labels" Workshops in conjunction with (CVPR), 2020
- o [C2] Unsupervised Intra-domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation through Self-Supervision Fei pan, Inkyu Shin, Francois Rameau, Seokju Lee, In So Kweon Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2020 (Oral)
- [C1] Image-to-Image Translation via Group-wise Deep Whitening-and-Coloring Transformation Wonwoong Cho, Sungha Choi, David Keetae Park, Inkyu Shin, Jaegul Choo Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2019 (Oral)

## IT skills

- Languages: Python, MATLAB, C, LATEX
- Libraries: PyTorch

#### References

In So Kweon, Professor, KAIST iskweon@kaist.ac.kr

### **Service**

Military Service: Graduated from US Army Sergeant school(WLC) as KATUSA.